North-South Badge
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
Come on!
I made a great discovery!
I might win the Nobel prize.
When the Northern ends of the magnet approach closer, they just repel away..
So do the Southern ends.
If S end and N end get closer
They stick together, see?
Isn't it interesting? I discovered it!
Oh, please! Who doesn't even know that simple thing?
I knew it already when I was in the Kindergarten. You're such a slowpoke!
Stop!
You jerk!
How dare you make fun of me in front of everyone! Stop, Nobita!
I'll make sure to remember this!
When you turn up next time, I will make sure to beat you!
Keep it in mind!
You're so talkative...
Doraemon, please do something, help me!
But what can I do?
You live in the same neighborhood and go to same school
no matter what, you would have to come face-to-face with him.
An idea! There's a way that you don't have to see each other!
Are you gonna take out some gadget?
It's North-South Badges!
How to use them?
if you stick this on your back...
You will be like a magnet, Southern ends go together.
and vise versa...
Let's conduct an experiment!
First, you have to put it on.
Stick one on Mum too.
Mum, Dad asked you to see him!
Oh?
what's up, dear?
What's going on?
See, she's repelled by the badge.
What are you doing there?
I don't care!
Why are you mad?
Ouch!
Come here dear, grab my hand!
Dear!
Dear, I want to hold you! Stop going farther away!
But my body just bounced away!
How ridiculous, you don't like me anymore?
Dear, don't run!
They ended up fighting each other.
what should we do?
Now we just have to change one of the badges.
It's weird, I can't approach you for some reason.
Dear!
Happy ending for Mum and Dad!
Now you understand....
You stick South badge on your back...
and stick the South badge on Giant's back as well.
Now let me go stick this on him!
I see!
Now Giant ain't got a thing on me!
Is it okay for you to be here?
I'm not afraid at all.
Giant said he's going to tear you up to pieces!
Well, he can try it if he can!
Things have got really interesting!
Now I just have to provoke Giant!
What?
Nobita you jerk, I am going to tear you up!
Giant, I saw Nobita over there!
Okay!
It's show time!
Stop right there, Nobita!
Hey!
We're so close!
Where is the badge?
It's not on him yet.
Damn you!
I got you!
Nobita ran away very quickly.
How handy the badges are!
An idea! Lend me some more badges!
Why do you need them?
I'm going to make very good use of 'em!
There Shizuka-chan is.
Shizuka-chan!
Stop it.
Let me go!
Today I won't be pulled away so easily!!
Revenge for yesterday!
North-South Badge sure is powerful!
I stuck the wrong badge! I should have stuck this one! Sorry!
Sorry, Shizuka-chan
Nobita-kun, stop!
Just need to switch the badge.
I can't take it off!
I have to take off my shirt!
Huh, where is Shizuka-chan?
Shizuka-chan!
Don't worry, you can come out now.
Where are you?
GIant is chasing me!
Help me!
Doraemon, help me out, please do something!
Get Giant down!
If you can't, just switch Giant and Shizuka-chan!
Hurry up, Doraemon!
Shizuka-chan!
I told you not to use it to fool around.
I don't care about you anymore!